NDIANEKWU CHINEDU WILLIAMS

No 91a ARAKALE ROAD, AKURE, ONDO STATE.

chineduorganisaction@gmail.com

+2348179605715

OBJECTIVE

I am an experienced software developer who lives in Nigeria and seeking employment with a fast-growing or established startup. I bring more than three years experience writing JavaScript and more than two years experience in the technology industry on different scale of skills.

EXPERIENCE

INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE

2018 - 2019

GEO-INFORMATION SYSTEM

I worked as a G.I.S operator to navigation rough and vegetation plains to study the geographical structure of such areas.

FIVERR

2018 - Present

FREELANCE

I work as a freelance for both web and application designs developer on Fiverr.

EDUCATION

EDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY, AKURE.

2021

URBAN AND REGIONAL PLANNING

SACRED HEART SEMINARY, AKURE

2007 - 2013

COLLEGE DEGREE

DYNAMIC INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL

1999 - 2006

PRIMARY DEGREE

PROJECTS

Data-management api

I built a data-management api on my GitHub which was used in the development of a counter app.

Result: The client was satisfied with the job and referred me

UI/Ux design

I developed a customer based interface for medical patients to use in cases of emergencies.

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

NODE.JS

REACT-NATIVE

PYTHON

REFERENCE

Mr Jude Ndianekwu - "GLOBEC W.A LTD"

CEO

Unicetintlco@yahoo.com +2348034026305